Here's my solution for the explained variance equation.
下面说说我是如何计算解释的方差的
First, I need to know which S-values to look
首先 我需要知道
at as far as our top components are concerned.
对于前几位的成分 应该查看哪些 s 值
Now, these are in reverse order,
它们在传入的
and are parsed in as DataFame.
DataFame 中是倒序的
So for the top say, three components,
例如 对于前三个成分
I want the last three values in the parsed in as DataFrame,
我需要查看传入的 DataFrame 中的最后三个值
and I can get this index by getting our N-COMPONENTS
这个索引等于 N-COMPONENTS (33)
33 minus the n_ top_components that are parsed in here.
减去这里传入的 n_ top_components
So 33 minus 3 will result in an index of 30, for example.
33 - 3 = 30
You could also choose to just iterate through each row of S in reverse,
还可以反向遍历 s 的每行
and this is just one solution.
这只是一种方式
Then to calculate the explained approximate variance,
为了计算解释的近似方差
I'm going to use this equation from above.
我将使用上面的这个方程
This exact equation is for the top five components,
这个方程专门计算前五个成分
but I want to generalize for any number of n_top_components.
但是我希望延伸到任何数量的 n_top_components
So to get s squared for my top_n components,
为了计算前 n 个成分的平方
and getting the values from my start_index on,
并获得从 start_index 到结束的值
and I'm squaring them with np.square,
我用 np.square() 对它们求平分
and summing those values up.
并求和
Then I'm dividing by the square values over our entire SRA and summing those up.
然后除以整个 SRA 的平方和
This will return something that holds a value at the index zero,
这样会返回一个在索引 0 处存储值的结果
and I'm returning that one value here.
在这里返回这个值
Here, I'm calling the explained variance function that I just defined.
在这里调用刚刚创建的 explained_variance 函数
I'm parsing in s or DataFrame from above and a number of top components.
传入上面的 DataFrame s 和前几个成分的数量
I was just try to see what the variance is for the very top component first.
我只是想查看最高成分解释的方差
For just the top principal component,
对于最高的主成分
I get unexplained variance of about 32 percent.
解释的方差约为 32%
Recall that I want to find the number of top N_COMPONENTS
我的目标是寻找能解释约 80% 的
that cover about 80 percent of our data variance,
数据方差的前 n 个成分
and I will use a mix of trial and error and also start with educated guess here.
我将通过试错法并从有根据地推测开始
Now, I know our current data has 34 features listed here,
我知道当前数据在这里列出了 34 个特征
and this is just our feature list from the columns in our scaled counties DataFrame.
这个特征列表来自 scaled_counties DataFrame
But I suspect that many of these are correlated or redundant.
但是我怀疑有很多特征是相关的或多余的
In fact, I can basically see a few big genres here.
实际上 肉眼就可以看出大的类别
I can see details about the total population,
可以看到关于总人口
a simple gender, and race breakdown,
性别和种族
as well as details about income level,
以及收入水平
profession, transit type, and work employment type.
职业 交通方式和就业类型的详情
So I'm actually thinking that a good number of
我猜测合适的前几个成分数量
top components will be around seven or eight,
应该约为 7 或 8 个
and I can test that out.
测试下
In fact, I can see that the explained variance for
可以看到前七个成分解释的方差
our top seven components is around 80 percent.
约为 80%
I wonder if I can go any lower.
看看还能少一个吗
It looks like the top six correspond to about 76 or 77 percent of variance.
前六个解释的方差约为 76% 或 77%
So I do want to capture the top seven.
所以需要保留前七个
So now, we know that the top seven components cover about 80 percent of my data variance,
现在我们知道前七个成分涵盖了约 80% 的数据方差
and I'll keep this number in mind and use it later to create some new training data.
我记下这个数字并在后面创建新的训练数据时使用它
Next, you may be wondering what makes up the seven components.
你可能会疑问 这七个成分是由哪些特征组成的？
What linear combinations of features make
什么样的特征线性组合
these components so influential in describing the spread of our data?
使这些成分对描述数据的分散性如此有影响？
So next, I'll show you how to take a look at the makeup of each of these top components.
接下来 我将介绍如何查看前几个成分的组成